University Council; Records ua100
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1964-1997, Undated; 4; 0.66 cubic ft.
  - Members Buhrmaster, Kenneth E., 1970 September-1975 December; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Members Cameron, Truman D., 1967 February (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Members Carlsan, C. Theodre, 1976 March-1976 April (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Members John F. Filippone/Looper, Victor, 1967 June-1974 January; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Members Hudson, Carl C., 1973 October-1976 April (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Members Athena C. Kouray, 1979 April; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Members Lee, Harry O, 1967 July-1978 February (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Members Loopers, Victor K., 1972 May-1979 August; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Members Posner, Elinore H., 1978 July-1978 August; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Members Straub, J. Vanderbilt, 1965 December-1979 February; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Member Wagner, Wayne E., 1971 September-1975 May; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Membership Lists, 1971 December-1979 October; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 October-1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Parking Committee, 1968 November-1972 September; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Resolutions, 1964 October-1981 March; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Rules and regulations, 1971 November-1975; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Members, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Naming Committee, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - University Council Actions/Resolutions, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Act Conference, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - University Council Committee on External Affairs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Financial and Physical Plant Sub committee, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - University Council Distinguished Service Medal, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Facilities Committee, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - University Council Member List, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - University Council-Powers and duties, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - University Council Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Naming Roadways, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Naming-Policy-Buildings Grounds, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Dr. Laman H. Bruner, Jr., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - C. Theodore Carlson, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Dr. Audrey B. Champagne, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Sue Faerman, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Fischer, Steven N., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Mrs. A. Rita Chandellier Glavin, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Richard A. Hanft, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Betty H. Hay, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Holt-Harris, John E., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Alan V. Iselin, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Larry Kayfmann, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Peter D. Kiernan, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Athena C. Kouray, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Lee Harry O., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Joy Longo, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Victor K Looper, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Athena V. Lord, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Martha W. Miller, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Poklemba, John J., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Joan E. Schulz, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - J. Vanderbilt Straub, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Lewis A. Swyer, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Tallcott, David M., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Vivian Throne, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Wayne E. Wagner, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Goldie L. Watkins, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Wellington, Caroline 6., Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Thomas M. Whalen, III, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)